Cody Moore

801.631.2946 | moorecody@mac.com | Salt Lake City, UT

Service industry/Photography Profile

Over 19 years in the restaurant industry with varied experience in casual to fine dining styles of service. Passion for & knowledge of beer culture, brewing processes, & appropriate food pairings genuine customer care style that reflects increased sales, satisfied guests, & ability to build a loyal clientele.

I am a dedicated Photographer exhibiting true love for craft, art, and science of photography process. Seasoned professional at using camera lenses, controls, and composition to capture stunning results. Consistently enhancing creative insight through projects and professional workshops. My Professional work includes portrait, wedding, and travel photography.

SKILLS

- Multitasking and Prioritization
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Photography and Videography
- Engaging Customers

employment experience

*Redrock Brewing Company | Salt Lake City, UT | Bartender & Server | June 2010 - November 2021.

Provides the highest quality customer service for patrons at one of Salt Lake's City's most well-known, high-volume gastropubs; expectation of each server is to maintain a section of up to 9 tables with average sales exceeding \$2,000 per shift. Possesses extensive knowledge of beer, wine, & cocktails and proper preparation & serving methods; bar service requires attentive multitasking in serving 21 seats while accommodating the beverage needs of 11 servers on the floor.

*St. Bernard's at Solitude Resort | Salt Lake City, UT | Bartender & Seasonal Server | November 2008 - February 2009 Exemplified skill & precision in 5-course dining & wine service at a fine-dining establishment at Solitude Mountain Resort for the winter season.

*Z-Tejas | Salt Lake City, UT | Bartender & Server | August 2006 - November 2009 Represented the Southwest-style dining establishment as both a server & bartender, meeting high expectations of table turn-around associated with the restaurant location near the convention center & major sports arena.

Education & Certifications

- University of Utah | Bachelors of Arts | Film & Photography | Graduated 2007
- Cicerone Beer Certification | Level 1 Food Handlers Permit & Alcohol Service Permit